<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mmagician</title><link>https://mmagician.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on mmagician</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://mmagician.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://mmagician.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 19:14:50 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://mmagician.github.io/about/</guid><description>About I currently work as a Technical Evaluator at the Web3 Foundation, evaluating Grants.
As a side project, I&amp;rsquo;m working on the Zero Knowledge Sudoku Game and running a few validator nodes.
When I&amp;rsquo;m not coding, I&amp;rsquo;m probably out doing some sports.</description></item><item><title>Hard Math Game</title><link>https://mmagician.github.io/hardmathgame/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 19:14:50 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://mmagician.github.io/hardmathgame/</guid><description>Hard Math Game Download from Google Play Store
(and no, I don&amp;rsquo;t need a new name)
Story When I was a teenager, I remember our math teacher would show us a game at the end of the class if we had extra time. He would project a series of slides onto a screen. On each slide, there were four squares, each with an integer on it. The goal of the game was coming up with a sequence of operations (only addition and multiplication were allowed) that would use all the four numbers and arrive at 24.</description></item><item><title>Validator</title><link>https://mmagician.github.io/validator/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 19:14:50 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://mmagician.github.io/validator/</guid><description>Network Validators It turns out that unwanted DevOps experience and on-call rotations have proven useful, after all!
Having deployed to AWS &amp;amp; Hetzner in my previous roles made it fairly easy to spin up a couple of validators.
I&amp;rsquo;m involved in validation services via two separate entities:
AMJ Stake, which aims to provide a trusted validator for both Kusama and Polkadot mmagician (myself), so far participating in the Kusama 1KV with two nodes Kusama As mmagician, I&amp;rsquo;m running two validators, which are both part of the 1K Validator Program.</description></item><item><title>ZK Sudoku Game</title><link>https://mmagician.github.io/smoothie/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 19:14:50 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://mmagician.github.io/smoothie/</guid><description>Smoothie - Sudoku Made Out Of The Hard mathematIcal Elements Zero Knowledge Proofs are still mysterious and hard to explain to non-cryptographers. I am building a user friendly platform to demonstrate the principle behind ZKPs as a game between a prover &amp;amp; a verifier.
To this end, I am using a well-known game of sudoku: users will solve the sudoku game in their browser and generate a proof of correctness. The verifier will be a smart contract that can verify the proofs and issue acknowledgements for valid solutions.</description></item></channel></rss>